Hello, my name is Alexandru Secareanu I am Web Developer

PHOTO

ABOUT ME

TECHNICAL SKILLS

I've been working as a programmer for almost 3 years. My main focus further developing and perfecting my skills, working on new software and learn as much as I can.

You can visit my website to learn more

about me: https://ap-

secareanu.github.io/portofolio/

FRONT-END

ReactJS EJS Tailwind SASS

BACK-END

NodeJS with ExpressJS

DATABASES

PostgreSQL(SQL)
MongoDB(noSQL)

OTHERS

TypeScript Webpack Linux Figma

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Date of birth: 02 of July 1998 Birthplace: Bucharest, Romania Languages: Romanian, English (C1)

WORK EXPERIENCE

Web Developer at Digital Star

Jan. 2022 - Present

In this company, I've been working in developing Frontend and Back-end for website for several clients, using:

- HTML/CSS
- SASS
- PHP

Technical Support Agent at CGS Romania

July 2019 - March 2021

In this company, I was assisting Sprint U.S. customers with technical related issues such as lack of data. After 6 months, I was promoted to **Technical Support Escalations Agent**. On this related role, I was assisting my colleagues with clients by providing necessary information to solve the issue as perfect as possible.

Personal skill development

Mar. 2021 - Present

Since I started learning Web Development, I've been constantly learning new technologies, developing small projects to further develop and perfect my technical skills. Some of those skills are:

- TypeScript
- Back-End development with NodeJS and ExpressJS
- Databases with PostgreSQL and MongoDB
- Project optimization with Webpack

Quality Assurance Agent at Ubisoft

Mar. 2018 - July 2018

At this company, I was testing various builds for Ubisoft's in-development games and patches for already launched games and reporting found bugs and issues back to the development team.

+40 728 435 738

EDUCATION	HOBBIES	CONTACT INFO
Faculty of Informatics Sep 2023 - Present I am currently studying computer science at Titu Maiorescu University Faculty of Foreign Languages and Literatures Sep 2018 - July 2021 Studied Polish and English Languages	Cycling and martial arts Gaming and modding games Reverse engineering Astronomy	EMAIL secareanu.alexandru98@gmail.com WEBSITE https://ap-secareanu.github.io /portofolio/ LINKEDIN https://www.linkedin.com/in/secarea nu-alexandru-bb97921b8 PHONE